# Eginata Kasan

+61 451 059 799  $\cdot$  <u>eginatakasan@gmail.com</u>  $\cdot$  <u>eginatakasan.github.io</u>  $\cdot$  <u>Linkedin</u> 710 George Street, Haymarket, NSW 2000

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm currently studying Master of Information Technology at UTS, Sydney. An experienced software engineer, I worked at Nomura Research Institute (NRI) Indonesia for over 2 years and interned as a Game Developer at Agate Studio. A firm believer in the spirit of teamwork, I enjoy collaborating with others to drive towards meaningful objectives.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UX Engineer October 2021 - January 2024

#### Nomura Research Institute Indonesia, Jakarta, Indonesia

- Front-end development with emphasis on UI precision & UX improvement
- Mobile app developments with React Native and responsive/fluid website development with React, Vue, and pure HTML/CSS/JS
- Developed UI library for company with Storybook
- · High attention to micro-interactions
- Worked on multiple projects from national & international clients
- Collaborated with different teams, consisting of project owners, managers and co-workers from Indonesia and Japan

## **Games Programmer Intern**

June 2019 - August 2019

## Agate Games Studio, Bandung, Indonesia

- Worked with a team of four to develop company framework using Unity (C#) and Google Firebase
- Was awarded a Golden Ticket distinction for a job well done

#### **EDUCATION**

## Master of Information Technology

February 2024 - Current

## **University of Technology Sydney (UTS)**

- Awardee of UTS Postgraduate Academic Excellence International Scholarship
- · Majoring in Interactive Media

#### **Bachelor of Computer Science**

July 2017 - July 2021

## **Bandung Institute of Technology**

- Wrote dissertation on metrics to quantify User Experience in e-commerce
- Head of Algorithm for Fire Extinguisher Robot Team (2018)

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## Frameworks

Web Development: React, Vue.js, Wordpress (PHP), Redux, Tailwind, CSS, Sass

Mobile Development: React Native, Android Studio, Unity, Nativewind

## Languages

Javascript/Typescript, HTML/CSS, Java, Python, C#, C++, PHP

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Google's Foundation of UX Design June 2023

Coursera

<u>Dynamic User Experience: Dynamic and Usability</u>

January 2023

**Interaction Design Foundation** 

<u>Design for the 21th Century with Don Norman</u>

January 2023

**Interaction Design Foundation** 

Mobile UX Design August 2022

**Interaction Design Foundation** 

#### **RELEVANT PROJECTS**

### Point of Sales Web App for Indonesian Startup

Frontend Development - ReactJS, Redux and Typescript

- Two web applications designed for restaurant management with printable QR, menus/table management and subscription admin
- Features include restaurant menu management, restaurant table management, admin panel, basic authentication, form validation and QR generation

## **Document Management Website**

Frontend Development - ReactJS, Redux and Typescript

- · Created a website for storing and sharing documents across users
- · Designed User Interface and UI kit for the website

## Fried Food Management Mobile App

Frontend Development - React Native, Redux, Typescript

- A mobile app for convenience store managers to reduce fried food waste by managing food quantities and creation/disposal schedule
- Confronted UI challenge of complicated nested scroll tables and huge table inside modals
- Managed to improve overall application performance

## The Dentists Indonesia Wordpress site

Fullstack Development - Wordpress, Local, PHP, HTML/CSS, Javascript

- An admin-editable website providing information, services, FAQs and contacts for a local dentist clinic
- Can be visited through this link

#### **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Women in Engineering and IT Community

**UTS SOUL** 

**UTS Tech Society** 

#### REFERENCES

Available upon request